RG 005:034, Office of the Governor: John Dempsey (1961-1971)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 11. Speeches with related materials, 1961-1970
  - Large type copied marked for reading, 1961-1970
    - Housing and Redevelopment Conference, Northford, 1961 September 14 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Housing and Redevelopment Conference, Groton, 1962 June 24 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Industrial Management Clubs, "Top Management Night", New Haven, 1962 January 16 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Industrial Management Clubs, Joint Meeting Norwich & New London, Norwich, 1962 May 7 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Insurers Convention, Miami, Florida, 1964 November 17 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Interstate & Foreign Commerce, Committee on, Statement by Governor concerning Channel 3, Washington, D.C., 1962 March 7 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Interstate Highway 91, Rocky Hill to Meriden & section of Rt. 2A in Meriden, 1965 October 27 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Italy, Order Sons of, State Convention, Danbury, 1965 May 16 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Japan, Northeast State Conference on Exports, Hartford, 1962 April 2 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1961 March 4 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1962 February 17 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Junior Achievement, Hartford, 1965 November 19 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Killingly High School, Graduation, 1965 June 17 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Kiwanis, New England District Convention, Groton, 1961 September 16 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Labor Council Convention, State, Hartford, 1961 September 6 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Labor Council Convention, State, Hartford, 1961 September 5 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Labor Council Convention, State, Hartford, 1961 September 4 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Labor Council Convention, State, Bridgeport, 1964 September 11 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Labor Council Convention, State, Hartford, 1965 September 15 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Law Day, Stamford, 1962 May 1 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Long Lane School, Dedication for McConaughy Hall & Briggs Home, 1961 May 13 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Loyalty Day Program, Norwalk, 1961 April 30 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Manchester Chamber of Commerce, 1964 April 15 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mansfield State Training School, Dedication of Bennet Hall, 1964 January 12 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Manson Laboratories, Wilton, 1964 June 17 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, New Haven, 1962 September 11 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Manufacturers Association of Hartford County, Hartford, 1965 May 24 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, New Haven, 1965 September 9 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mental Deficiency, American Association, Northeastern Regional Conference, Groton, 1963 September 16 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mental Health, Connecticut Association, Newington, 1964 June 4 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mental Health, Dedication of Franklin S. DuBois Day Treatment Center, speech delivered by Lt. Gov., Stamford, 1964 May 27 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mental Health, Testimony at hearing of Interstate Commerce Committee on Mental health aid bill, Washington, D.C., 1965 March 4 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mental Health Council, Middlesex Area, Middletown, 1965 March 29 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mental Health Congress, Hartford, 1965 November 4 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mental Retardation, New Haven Regional Center for Mentally Retarded, New Haven, 1964 June 23 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mental Retardation, Greater Hartford Center, Newington, 1965 May 7 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mental Retardation, Connecticut Association for Retarded Children Annual Convention, Bridgeport, 1965 October 23 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Methodist Youth Fellowship Rally, Hartford, 1964 April 26 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Meriden, Willow Court Housing Project, 1964 July 30 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Metropolitan Regional Council Law Enforcement Committee, Stamford, 1964 March 27 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Mills, Lewis S. High School, Dedication Ceremonies, Burlington, 1961 November 26 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - Moran, James H. Junior High School, Dedication Ceremonies, Wallingford, 1962 April 15 (Box Volume 6 (A-440))
    - National Safety Council, Chicago, 1961 October 17 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - Naugatuck News, Dedication of new plant, 1965 October 29 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - Naugatuck Valley Chamber of Commerce, Lower, Ansonia, 1965 April 21 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - New England Council, State Dinner, Boston, 1961 November 16 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - New England Council, State Dinner, Boston, 1965 November 18 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - New England Governors' Conference, Remarks at Governors' Luncheon, Boston, 1963 November 21 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - New England Governors' Conference, Remarks, Panel on Intergovernmental Relations & the New England States, Boston, 1963 November 22 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - New Haven Jewish Community Center, New Haven, 1965 March 24 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - New Haven Railroad, Testimony at hearing of U.S. Senate Committee on Commerce, Washington, D.C., 1965 March 4 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - New Haven Railroad, Presentation of Four-State Program, New York, 1965 March 26 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - New Haven Railroad, New England Governor's Conference, meeting with New England Congressional Delegation, Washington, D.C., 1965 April 6 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - Newspaper Editors, New England Society of, Hartford, 1964 December 4 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - North Branford High School, 1965 June 24 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - Northwestern Connecticut Community College, Winsted, 1965 December 5 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - Norwalk Industrial Management Club, 1962 March 20 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - Norwich Hospital Chapel, Dedication, Preston, 1962 March 15 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - Norwich Area Industrial Management Club, Danielson, 1965 October 4 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - O'Brien, Archbishop, Silver Jubilee of Consecration, Hartford, 1965 May 26 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - Osborn, Stanley H. Library, Dedication Ceremony, Hartford, 1965 June 11 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - Otis Library, Dedication, Norwich, 1962 August 6 (Box Volume 7 (A-441))
    - Police, Connecticut Chiefs of, Academy Graduation, Bethany, 1965 June 18 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Polish National Alliance, Lodge 830, 50th Anniversary of Alliance College, Stamford, 1962 October 20 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Portland High School, Dedication, 1961 November 5 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Postmaster, Connecticut Chapter, National Association, Cheshire, 1965 November 13 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Powder House Day, and 190th Anniversary, Second Company, Governor's Foot Guard, New Haven, 1965 May 22 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Prentice-Hall Corporation, Waterford, 1961 October 2 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Printing Week Banquet, Hartford, 1962 January 18 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Probation & Parole Association, State Capitol, 1964 October 20 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Providence College, New Haven Alumni, Veritas Award Dinner, 1961 April 5 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Providence College, 1963 June 4 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Putnam Area Chamber of Commerce, Putnam, 1965 February 6 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Putnam High School, Graduation, 1962 June 15 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Real Estate Boards, Connecticut Association of, Hartford, 1961 September 28 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Real Estate Boards, Connecticut Association of, Hartford, 1964 September 17 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Real Estate Board, New Haven, Hamden, 1962 October 18 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Red Cross, Greater Hartford Chapter, Hartford, 1965 November 10 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, South Windsor, 1961 December 15 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Research Symposium, Hartford, 1962 June 4 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Re-training Committee, Mayor's Job, New Haven, 1962 March 12 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Ridgefield Library, Dedication of new wing, 1963 November 7 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Road Builders Association, Connecticut, Cheshire, 1965 December 8 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Rockville Housing Project, Franklin Park, 1964 September 30 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Saint Anselm's College, Commencement, New Hampshire, 1962 June 11 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - St. Bernard's High School, Graduation, New London, 1962 June 10 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - St. Joseph College, Dedication of Gengras Center for Exceptional Children, 1965 December 8 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - St. Onge, William Campaign Dinner, Putnam, 1964 August 9 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Sam Eddy Field, Dedication, North Canaan, 1962 May 27 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Scientific Symposium, Connecticut Academy of General Practices, 1961 October 5 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Service Bureau for Women's Organizations, East Berlin, 1963 November 14 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Smaller Manufacturers Association of Waterbury, 1961 October 9 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Social Workers, Connecticut Conference of, Hartford, 1961 November 8 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Social Work, Connecticut Conference of, Hartford, 1962 October 31 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Social Workers, National Association Connecticut Chapter, Newington, 1961 October 10 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Sons of the American Revolution, Connecticut Society of, Hartford, 1964 February 22 (Box Volume 8 (A-442))
    - Sprague, Centennial Celebration, 1961 April 29 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Stamford Chamber of Commerce, Darien, 1962 October 15 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Stamford Chamber of Commerce, Darien, 1965 May 12 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - State Chamber of Commerce, 1961 November 21 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - State Chamber of Commerce, 1965 November 16 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - State Employees Association, Hartford, 1961 October 15 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - State Employees Association, Hartford, 1962 October 14 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - State Employees Association, Hartford, 1963 October 13 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - State Employees Association, Hartford, 1964 October 18 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - State Employees Association, Hartford, 1965 October 17 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - State Police Auxiliary Meeting, Hartford, 1961 August 30 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - State Police Auxiliary, Hartford, 1962 August 30 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - State Safety Commission, Hartford, 1962 June 26 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Superior Industries, West Haven, 1962 October 24 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Telephone Workers, Connecticut Union of, Old Saybrook, 1962 September 18 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Temple Beth Israel Men's Club, West Hartford, 1965 April 19 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Temple Mishkan Israel, Hamden, 1961 December 13 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Thomaston Flood Control Dam, Dedication Ceremonies, 1961 June 16 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Thursday Ministers' Club, 1961 September 14 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Thursday Ministers' Club, 1962 October 11 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Thursday Ministers' Club, 1963 October 17 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Tolland, 250th Anniversary of Town, 1965 June 27 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Torrington Branch, University of Connecticut, Dedication, 1965 October 20 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Torrington, Dedication of Thompson Heights Housing Project for Elderly, 1965 September 30 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Town Clerks Association, Willimantic, 1961 October 20 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Traffic Safety Award Luncheon, Hartford, 1961 September 25 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Traffic Safety Conference, State Capitol, Hartford, 1961 July 14 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Traffic Safety Conference, Yale University, New Haven, 1962 March 31 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Traffic Safety Conference, Central Connecticut State College, New Britain, 1964 April 18 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - Transportation, Mass, Capitol Region Conference, Connecticut General Life Insurance Company, Bloomfield, 1961 December 1 (Box Volume 9 (A-443))
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Savings Bond Luncheon, East Hartford, 1965 October 28 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - University of Connecticut, Commencement Address, 1964 June 14 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - University of Connecticut, Inauguration of Dr. Babbidge, 1962 October 20 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - University of Connecticut, Men's Faculty Club, 1962 March 29 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - University of Hartford, Young Democratic Club, 1962 May 11 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Waterbury, Democratic Party, 1965 October 31 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Waterbury Dental Society, Cheshire, 1962 April 10 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Waterbury State Technical Institute, Waterbury, 1962 July 12 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Water Pollution Hearing, Natural Resources & Power Subcommittee of the House Government Operations Committee, Federal Building, Hartford, 1963 October 4 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Welfare Association, American Public, Hartford, 1963 September 11 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Westhill Gardens, Dedication, Home for Elderly, Manchester, 1962 June 24 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - West Thompson Dam, Dedication, 1965 October 2 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Women's Press Club of New York City, New York, 1965 March 27 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Xavier High School, Dedication, Middletown, 1963 September 7 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Yankee Expressway, Interstate 84, Danbury, Opening Ceremonies, 1961 December 16 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Yankee Expressway, Interstate 84, Waterbury, Opening Ceremonies, 1961 December 16 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Young Democrats Convention, Bridgeport, 1964 April 18 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Youth Traffic Safety Conference, New Britain, 1965 October 29 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Youth Traffic Safety Conference, New Haven, 1964 October 30 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Youth Traffic Safety Conference, Bloomfield, 1963 October 25 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
    - Youth Traffic Safety Conference, Hartford, 1965 October 26 (Box Volume 10 (A-444))
- Series 12. Official Statements, 1956-1970
  - Achievement Week (Box A-445)
  - Advertising Week (Box A-445)
  - Afro-Arts Cultural Center (Box A-445)
  - Air National Guard Day (Box A-445)
  - Alcoholism Information Week (Box A-445)
  - Alien Address Report Month (Box A-445)
  - Alliance for Progress Day (Box A-445)
  - Amateur Athletic Union (Box A-445)
  - Amateur Athletic Union (Box A-445)
  - Amaranth, Order of (Box A-445)
  - Amateur Radio Week (Box A-445)
  - Amateur Soccer Week (Box A-445)
  - American Automobile Association Founders Day (Box A-445)
  - American Education Week (Box A-445)
  - American Football Coaches Association (Box A-445)
  - American Heritage Foundation (Get Out the Vote) (Box A-445)
  - American History Month (Box A-445)
  - American Institute of Banking (Box A-445)
  - American Jewish Congress Week (Box A-445)
  - American Legion (Box A-445)
  - American Medical Center at Denver Day (Box A-445)
  - American Music Month (Box A-445)
  - American Patent Law Month (Box A-445)
  - American War Mothers Coronation Day, 1956 May 12 (Box A-445)
  - American Women in Radio and Television Week (Box A-445)
  - Outdoor Amusement Park Week (Box A-445)
  - Anchor Club (Box A-445)
  - Ann Sullivan Week (Box A-445)
  - Apprenticeship Month (Box A-445)
  - Arbor Day (Box A-445)
  - Architectural Barriers Day (Box A-445)
  - Armed Forces Day and Week (Box A-445)
  - Armed Forces Week (Box A-445)
  - Armenian Independence Day (Box A-445)
  - Army Nurse Enlistment Month (Box A-445)
  - Army Reserve Month (Box A-445)
  - Art Week (American) (Box A-446)
  - Assessors Week (Box A-446)
  - Automatic Merchandise Month (Box A-446)
  - Autorama (Box A-446)
  - Aviation Week (Box A-446)
  - Back to School Week (Box A-446)
  - B"nai B"rith Youth Organization Week (Box A-446)
  - Baha'i Week, 1966 April 22-29 (Box A-446)
  - Baltic Day (Box A-446)
  - Banana Week (Box A-446)
  - Barber Shop Harmony Week (Box A-446)
  - Barnum Festival (Box A-446)
  - John Barry Day, 1960 September 13 (Box A-446)
  - Bataan Day (Box A-446)
  - Battle Flag Day (Box A-446)
  - Beauty Career Day (Box A-446)
  - National Beauty Salon Week (Box A-446)
  - Be Kind to Animals Week (Box A-446)
  - Bells Across the Nation Day, 1962 April 19 (Box A-446)
  - Better Record Keeping Month (Box A-446)
  - Biafra, Hope for (Box A-446)
  - Bible Week (Box A-446)
  - American Bike Month (Box A-446)
  - Bill of Rights Day (Box A-446)
  - B"nai B"rith Membership Month (Box A-446)
  - Bowdoin Day, 1959 June 27 (Box A-446)
  - Bowling Week (Box A-446)
  - Boys Club, Good Will Charter Oak Building Fund, 1955 November 2 (Box A-446)
  - Boys Club Week (Box A-446)
  - Boy Scouts Week, 1961-1964 (Box A-446)
  - Boy Scout Week #2, 1965-1966 (Box A-447)
  - Boynton, Paul M. (Day), 1970 May 2 (Box A-447)
  - Brand Names Week (Box A-447)
  - Membership Week, Brandeis University National Women's Committee (Box A-447)
  - Brasher, Rex (Day) (Box A-447)
  - Bring 'em Back Alive Campaign, 1968 June 30-September 7 (Box A-447)
  - Brotherhood Week (Box A-447)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council (Box A-447)
  - Business Women Week (Box A-447)
  - Business Education Day (Box A-447)
  - Byelorussian Independence Day (Box A-447)
  - Campfire Girls (Box A-447)
  - Cancelled Education Week (Box A-447)
  - Career Opportunities for College Students Week (Box A-447)
  - Children's Asthma Week (Box A-447)
  - Carl Yastrzemski Week (Box A-447)
  - Carpi Diem Fraternity (Box A-447)
  - Carver, George Washington Week (Box A-447)
  - Cat Week (Box A-447)
  - Catholic Book Week (Box A-447)
  - Catholic Graduates Club of Greater Hartford (Box A-447)
  - Catholic Youth's Week (Box A-447)
  - Centennial Legion of Historic Military Commands, Inc. (Box A-447)
  - Central Conn. Safe Day (Box A-447)
  - Cerebral Palsy (Box A-447)
  - Certified Eating Places (Box A-447)
  - Chamber of Commerce Week (Box A-448)
  - Chemical Progress Week (Box A-448)
  - Children's Art Month (Box A-448)
  - Child Safety Week (Box A-448)
  - Child Health Week (Box A-448)
  - Children's Day (Box A-448)
  - Children's Dental Health Week (Box A-448)
  - Children's Services Horse Show (Box A-448)
  - Children's Day for Youth Aliyah (Box A-448)
  - Child Welfare Week (Box A-448)
  - Christmas Seal Campaign (Box A-448)
  - Church of God in Christ International Day, 1970 August 5 (Box A-448)
  - Citizens Concern for Crime Week (Box A-448)
  - Citizenship Day (Box A-448)
  - City of Hope (Box A-448)
  - Civilian Air Patrol Week (Box A-448)
  - Civil Defense Day (Box A-448)
  - Cleaner Air Week (Box A-448)
  - Clergy Week (Box A-449)
  - Color Guard Week (Box A-449)
  - Colt's Patent Firearms Manufacturing Co., Inc. (Box A-449)
  - Coin Week (Box A-449)
  - Columbian Squires Week (Box A-449)
  - Columbus Day (Box A-449)
  - Community Ambassador Project: Statement by Gov. Ribicoff, 1956 April 12 (Box A-449)
  - Community Development Month (Box A-449)
  - Community Health Week (Box A-449)
  - Conn. Charter Day, 1962 May 10 (Box A-449)
  - Conn. Circle - Harry F. Morse, Publisher and Editor (Box A-449)
  - Conn. Holidays - Publication (Box A-449)
  - Conn. - Japan Trade Week, 1965 March 28-April 2 (Box A-449)
  - Conn. Municipal Manual (Box A-449)
  - Conn. Safety Commission 30th Anniversary (Box A-449)
  - Conservation District Week (Box A-449)
  - Constitution Week (Box A-449)
  - Coop Month (Box A-449)
  - Construction Industry Exposition, 1964 April 14-15 (Box A-449)
  - Consumer Education Month (Box A-449)
  - Convalescent Hospital Week (Box A-449)
  - County Fair and Bazaar (Box A-449)
  - Country Music Week (Box A-449)
  - Courtesy Week, 1961 November 6-11 (Box A-449)
  - Credit Union Day, 1961 October 19 (Box A-449)
  - Crime Prevention Week, 1956 February 12-18 (Box A-449)
  - Wilbur Cross Day, 1962 April 10 (Box A-449)
  - Culinary Arts Week (Box A-449)
  - Currency Act Centennial (Box A-449)
  - Curtiss Johnson Publications (Box A-449)
  - Cystic Fibrosis (Box A-449)
  - Czechoslovak Culture (Box A-449)
  - D for Decency Week (Box A-449)
  - Dairy Month (Box A-449)
  - Data Processing Week (Box A-449)
  - Day of Bread (Box A-449)
  - Day of Prayer for Peace and Reconciliation (Box A-449)
  - DECA Week (Distributive Education Clubs of America) (Box A-449)
  - Demolay Week, 1962 March 11-18 (Box A-449)
  - Denmark (Box A-449)
  - Dental Laboratory Week (Box A-449)
  - Digest of Administrative Reports (Box A-449)
  - Disabled American Veterans - Idento Tags (Box A-449)
  - Discover America, Vacation Planning Time (Box A-449)
  - Conn. Distributive Education Week (Box A-449)
  - Dorchester Day (Box A-449)
  - Drum Corps Week (Box A-449)
  - Amelia Earhart Week, 1960 January 5-11 (Box A-449)
  - Earth Day (Box A-449)
  - Easter Seal Campaign (Box A-450)
  - East Hartford Women's Club (Community Safety Day & Exhibit) (Box A-450)
  - Eastern Orthodox Easter (Box A-450)
  - Eastern States Exposition (Conn. Day), 1970 September 23 (Box A-450)
  - Edison, Thomas Alvah (Box A-450)
  - Educational Television Month (Box A-450)
  - Eisenhower Golden Wedding Day (Box A-450)
  - Electronics Week throughout New England (Box A-450)
  - Elks (Box A-450)
  - Emancipation Proclamation Day (Box A-450)
  - Emergencies Don't Wait Week (Box A-450)
  - National Employ the Handicapped Week (Box A-450)
  - Engineers" Week (Box A-450)
  - Epilepsy Information Month (Box A-450)
  - Equal Opportunity Day (Box A-450)
  - Erikson Leif (Day), 1966 (Box A-450)
  - Estonian Freedom Day, 1966 February 24 (Box A-450)
  - Eugene O'Neill Memorial Week (Box A-450)
  - Exceptional Children's Week (Box A-450)
  - Exchange Ambassadors Program (Box A-450)
  - Extended Health Care Week (Box A-450)
  - Eye Bank Week (Box A-450)
  - Family Doctor Week (Box A-450)
  - Family Fishing Month, 1969 June (Box A-450)
  - Family Health Week (Box A-450)
  - Family Rehabilitation Program (Box A-450)
  - Family Week (Box A-450)
  - Farm Bureau Week, 1969 November 16-22 (Box A-450)
  - Father's Day (Box A-450)
  - Federal Aviation Day (Box A-450)
  - Fifers and Drummers Day (Box A-450)
  - Fire Prevention Day (Box A-450)
  - Fire Service Day, 1958 May 4 (Box A-451)
  - First Church of Christ - Hartford, Conn. (Box A-451)
  - First Congregational Church of Windham Center (Box A-451)
  - Youth Fitness Week (Box A-451)
  - Flag Day (Box A-451)
  - Flame of Hope Day, 1968 December 15 (Box A-451)
  - International Food Festival (Box A-451)
  - Football Hall of Fame (Box A-451)
  - Foot Health Week and Month (Box A-451)
  - Ford, Henry re: Henry Ford Day, 1963 July 30 (Box A-451)
  - Ford's Theater Day (Box A-451)
  - Foreign Language Week (Box A-451)
  - Forest Products Week (Box A-451)
  - Forty-Third Infantry Division Day (Box A-451)
  - Foster Parents Day (Box A-451)
  - Foster Parents Day, Statement by Gov. Ribicoff (Box A-451)
  - Four-H Club Week (Box A-451)
  - Fourth of July Highway Safety Statement (For the New Era, Deep River) (Box A-451)
  - Francis Scott Key (Box A-451)
  - Francisco, Peter (Box A-451)
  - Franco-American Message from Gov. Ribicoff to their 40th Convention (Box A-451)
  - Fraternal Week (Box A-451)
  - Free Cuba Day (Box A-451)
  - Freedom Day, March on Washington, D.C., 1963 August 28 (Box A-451)
  - Freedom from Hunger Week (Box A-451)
  - Freedom of Enterprise Week (Box A-451)
  - Freedom of Residence Days, 1965 March 18-20 (Box A-451)
  - Free World Friendship Week (Box A-451)
  - Freedom Bond Month (Box A-451)
  - Freedom Day (Box A-451)
  - Philadelphia's Freedom Week (Box A-451)
  - Freedom's Roll Call (Box A-451)
  - Free Enterprise Day (Box A-451)
  - French Opera Week (Box A-451)
  - Future Business Leaders of America (Box A-451)